<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><news>
<month><date>October 2012</date>
<news-item>Our newest book "The Octonauts Explore the Great Big Ocean" is OUT!! This big book is packed with fun & surprises - learn more at <a href="http://www.octonauts.com" target="new">Octonauts.com</a></news-item>
<news-item>Season 2 of Octonauts TV is launching -very- soon also. Explore! Rescue! Protect!</news-item></month>

<month><date>June 2012</date>
<news-item>Just wrapped up our latest Octonauts book (coming out this FALL!!) We'll try to post more sneakpeeks up on our facebook. It's going to be BIG and FUN with surprise Glow-in-the-dark page!</news-item>
<news-item>Meanwhile, Octonauts S2 is going full steam and keeping us busy!</news-item></month>
<month><date>November 2011</date>
<news-item><a href="https://www.myibend.com/cart/checkout/" target="new">Meomi iBends are back in stock!</a> A great stocking stuffer for your favourite geek. ;o) Use promo code MEOMI888 to get 15% off.</news-item>
<news-item>We are busybusy : ) Octonauts Season 2 has been greenlit (hooray!) and working on new octo-books. Undersea is the place to be!</news-item>
</month>
<month><date>September 2011</date>
<news-item>We now have a <a href="http://www.facebook.com/octonauts" target="new">Meomi Society6 page</a> where you can order art prints, skins, & shirts with art from Cloudseeders, Octonauts, & more! We'll be adding more art in the future, follow us for updates!</news-item>

<news-item>Our Octonauts books "Frown Fish" & "Great Ghost Reef" are now available in German, Swedish, Finnish and Norwegian! <a href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10150274941226923.332531.97570906922&type=1" target="new">See photos on our facebook!</a> Oktonauten / Oktonauterna / Oktonautit / Oktonautene</news-item>
</month>

<month><date>July 2011</date>
<news-item>Fisher-Price Octonauts toys are OUT now in the UK!! And they are awesome. :o) We're hosting a series of contests on the <a href="http://www.facebook.com/octonauts" target="new">Octonauts facebook page</a> - come join in the fun!</news-item>

<news-item>First three Os Octonautas books has just been launched in Brazil! <a href="http://www.octonautas.com" target="new">Visit the OCTONAUTAS site for more info!</a></news-item>
</month>

<month><date>May 2011</date>
<news-item>We're delighted to be part of the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=146142905458895" target="new">Vancouver 125th Anniversary t-shirt show at Tees.ca, opening on June 3rd, 6 - 10pm!</a> Lovely pieces by Vancouver artists such as Luc Latulippe, Mia Hansen, Atomos, Eboy, Chris vons Zombathy, GS Olsen, Hamburger Disco, Tony Cliff... and US! ^__^ We hope you'll drop by and say hi!</news-item>

<news-item>The UK edition of <a href="http://www.octonauts.com/book.html" target="new">The Octonauts & the Great Ghost Reef</a> by Meomi has just been released! Inspired by a real phenomenon where coral reefs lose their colour and turn white, this book sees our crew helping a sea turtle bring an endangered coral reef back to health. </news-item>
</month>

<month><date>February 2011</date>
<news-item>We're happy to share that we have <a href="http://printitgallery.com/artGalleryArtist.php?pId=167&pPag=0&pLang=2" target="new">new limited ed. art prints with PrintIT Gallery! </a> PrintIT makes gorgeous large prints on textile stretched on a simple aluminum frame -- featuring art from Octonauts and Cloudseeders!</news-item>
</month>

<month><date>January 2011</date>
<news-item>The TV ratings for The Octonauts are in! After 6 weeks, it is the No. 1 preschool show in the UK! The show  currently airs in the UK, France, Ireland, Australia, and Latin America with more countries coming later this year! <a href="http://www.facebook.com/octonauts/" target="new">Join the Octonauts facebook</a> for news and fun! Undersea adventures ahoy! </news-item>
<news-item>Our first series of <a href="http://www.myibend.com/" target="new">iBends</a> have sold out - but we're working on new ones, including iBendXL for ipads! </news-item>
</month>

<month><date>October 2010</date>
<news-item>We're excited to announce that the Octonauts animated preschool series has launched! You can find it currently airing on CBeebies (UK) TF1 (France: Les Octonauts ) Discovery Kids (Latin America: Octonautas ) with more countries to come. <a href="http://www.facebook.com/octonauts/" target="new">Join us on the Octonauts facebook</a> for news and fun! Undersea adventures ahoy! </news-item>
</month>

<month><date>April 2010</date>
<news-item>We have a <a href="http://www.surfacecollective.com/product-list/full-color/33/" target="new">new line of wall stickers</a> with Surface Collective - customize your walls with baby slothes, pandas,  snails and much more! </news-item>
</month>

<month><date>February 2010</date>
<news-item>Happy new years everyone! <a href="http://www.facebook.com/MEOMI/" target="new"> Join us on facebook</a> for Mascot Fridays as we count down to the Olympics! ^__^</news-item>
</month>

